[Music]
so
[Applause]
[Music]
um
[Applause]
[Music]
this
a clear is blue here
i feel completely new
[Music]
was here
and somehow now at last i
need
my own skin
up here
[Music]
there's so
much light here
light and space the sun's so bright here
upon my
as face
life seems to be somehow calling to me
from this strange new
world
steady as she goes
[Music]
brave sailor beware
is
[Music]
surrounded by nothing but water oh yes
it's simply delightful
the salt on your skin and the wind in
your hair and the waves as they ebb and
they flow
we're miles from the shore and guess
what i don't care as
[Music]
the ruler of all of the oceans is he in
mysterious fathoms below king of the sea
why that's nautical nonsense nothing but
a superstition
[Music]
the king of the ocean gets angry
and when he gets angry beware
i'm telling you lad when king triton is
mad how the waves will rock to and
fro hold on good luck as down you go
what is that
do you hear something oh my lord please
enough seafaring you've got to head back
to court to honor your father's dying
wish and take up his crown suppose i
don't want the crown oh you'd forsake
his kingdom all of his treasures
treasures
you mean like this
who needs it we drink straight out of
the bottle don't we boys
or this
not when we have the sun and the moon to
light our way
or this
no thanks grimsby i'd rather eat with my
bare hands you're a prince sire not a
common sailor these men are anything but
common grimsby
i'd rather be a sailor than a prince any
day
this is where i belong
everything seems so real here strange
how at home i feel here in the tides
swift flow
and when the pole is strong
i almost think i hear the sea
wild and free
calling me
from fathers
[Music]
there it is again
we ought to head back to shore your
majesty indeed we should not while i'm
captain now follow that voice to the
ends of the earth if you have to
aye aye
captain there's mermaids out there in
the bottomless blue and it's hay to the
starboard evil
watch out for a bladder you'll go to
your room in mysterious
[Music]
[Applause]
why
it's beautiful
hey ariel oh there you are
whoa
freaky
what's the matter haven't you been to
the surface before
yeah
sure
me and the other fish in my school we
come here all the time is that so
sure
we're not scared of
uh sharks
or boats
or fishermen
what a chum bucket
or those
you are afraid aren't you no
i'm not
i'm here now aren't i
with you
flounder you're blushing ah
it's a it's a sunburn
you get it up here are you flirting with
me
no way what if i was
oh
okay
hey guess what i found today
it was floating in the wake of a giant
ship treasure oh i'll say look
have you ever seen anything so amazing
in your entire life cool
what is it
i don't know
air speed check
altitude check
landing gear check
clear the runway
i know just who to ask
hello ariel hey scuttle look what we
found
more human paraphernicular eh you've
asked the right bird i happen to be an
expert on that very special can you tell
us what it's for
oh this is rare
redonkulously rare
insisting condition what what is it it's
a dinglehopper a tinglehopper
commonly used in saloons yes of the
beauty variety you see humans like to
wear their hair and tails pony or pig or
duck
a primp here and a twirl there and voila
a pompadour
and all thanks to
the dinglehopper i'll give you two same
dollars for it i don't know i'm telling
you kid out on the open sea you won't
get more than a few clams but i'm
prepared to offer i'm not selling
scuttle
i'm saving it for my collection
how's about a swap
i got something stupicious museum
quality really a banded
bulbous
snarf plant
second cousin to the tuba it makes music
sure thing kid i ain't just blowing
smoke it makes music so fantabulous so
absolutely marvel music oh no the
concert oh my gosh my father's gonna
kill me concert was the day i completely
forgot come on
thank you scuttle change your mind if
you want to sell you call me first
you're here
[Music]
benevolent murr folk creatures of the
deep today marks a special anniversary
for many years ago on this day i
inherited my father's kingdom and
banished the evil sea witch ursula
forever
[Music]
now may introduce the master of
ceremonies please
[Music]
you in store for us sebastian i got a
special song just for the occasion and
it's gonna be performed by none other
than your seven lovely daughters
why i wrote this little number for my
star pupil who might that be your
youngest adiel
such a voice that child
notes as clear as ice pictures pier as
water
why i haven't heard such magnificent
sounds since
well since her royal highness may she
rest in peace
you're gonna be a proud papa you'll see
if only she'd show up for rehearsal once
in a while let the merriments begin
[Music]
[Applause]
is
[Music]
oh
food
[Music]
[Applause]
my apologies sire but that girl she's
gonna be the death of me some women when
she should be singing
if i had this solo this never would have
happened that girl's angling for trouble
yeah she sure is i say give her the hook
fish puns aren't we better than that
honestly daddy you and ariel get away
with everything now now i love all of my
daughters equally oh please that answers
his candace tuna and twice as oily a
wrist is prettier than ariel andrina
smarter alanna sweeter attina is older
and adella
well
let's face it daddy you're the only male
attention adele's ever gonna get
hey what if you got that ariel doesn't
naked ambition and a willingness to kill
that's enough one zone sebastian was
that too much to hope for please sire
don't go pointing your puppies dreaded
at me
i'm sorry sebastian
you might go whipping up a hurricane by
mistake
well look what the catfish dragged in
daddy forgive me i'm so sorry ariel
young lady i just
forgot that's all as a result of your
careless and reckless behavior the whole
celebration was ruined completely
destroyed this concert was going to be
the pinnacle of my distinguished career
sebastian and now thanks to you i'm the
laughingstock of the whole kingdom
we give him a date with the whale of a
guy
i don't sing back up for anybody
mama loved me best but she
she's go
do you mind
please ariel you've been given such a
gift i know my mother's voice it's a
wondrous talent one that demands
stewardship and care
so please for the sake of her memory i
will daddy i promise no
it wasn't even ariel's fault that know
it all seagull started going on and on
you went to the surface again nothing
happened you could've been seen by one
of those barbarians one of those humans
daddy they're not barbarians crafts and
harpoons like you're not you're my baby
my youngest and i worry about you the
most i'm old enough to look after myself
as long as you live under my reef you'll
obey my rules if you just listen to me
for once that's the last time you will
ever swim to service again is that
understood you are so unfair
she's willful headstrong stubborn as a
barnacle
teenagers give them an inch andy swim
all over you
i can get her in my kingdom sebastian
but i can't raise my own daughter i was
too harsh she learned to fear me i don't
want that
she needs her mother sebastian and so do
i
[Music]
if only she were here
she'd know just what to say
she'd firmly and you gently help the
girl to find her way
she'd know what to forbid
and what we must allow
she'd have the strength and patience
that i lacked somehow
and oh what i would give to have her
back
now now sire it's difficult sure but you
gotta toughen up not meltdown for
audience sick i'm telling you that girl
needs constant supervision someone to
watch over her keep her out of trouble
say that's not a bad idea someone the
safeguard of every move
every dog battle every side stroke her
every time and you are just the crowd to
do it what you heard me from now on
ariel is your responsibility but your
majesty she's a clever mermaid i'm just
a crustacean
surely you want to pick someone higher
on the evolutionary scale
[Music]
a mistress of the deep beauty of the
brain
[Music]
my blowhole today my brother triton got
greedy that's all the day he stole my
half of the kingdom to think his very
own sister
and he double-crossed you
his own flesh and blood
casting you into exile a life of shame
and unceasing solitude in the shadowy
depths of the serpentine
all right all right don't blow your
fuses boys
it should have been mine
oh mine
when i was a kid a squirmy little squid
i was number seven born of seven little
girls seven little pearls so pretty as
could be perfect to a tea or except for
me
ugly as a slug a hideous hug daddy found
me lonesome and disgusting i could tell
they all got adored me i got ignored
stewie's guilty magic shell used to
belong to my grandpappy poseidon full of
lethal hexes and spells my little sea
snakes the perfect gift first burned
dangerously unstable child
most of all daddy loved one's sister
so feminine so fresh so fine
i would watch as he loved and kissed her
and i headed her guts from the bottom of
mine daddy's little angel daddy's little
sweet such a little friendly femme
she was seaweed in spice and everything
nice and i dreamed and i schemed
daddy's little angel how could i compete
with the girl so heaven said
just one spell from the shell and back
to her head she went
[Music]
thank you
next what did i do daughter number two
flung her in a whirlpool after spinning
round doctors three and four washed up
on the shore sadly five and six were
never found
but it didn't make my father love me
but it didn't bring me down oh no no no
it was sad that when dad caught that
very lethal flu
with no sisters in the line above me
yeah inheriting
oh a ton so much fun i forgot that my
dad also had an additional tot his son
still age one but i figured so what till
that's not news little baby groot
[Music]
a male heir
as soon as he came of age he stole
everything from me
every ocean every lake every pond every
puddle
but my dear flotsam and jetsam it's time
that i took revenge
revenge on what he loves most
[Music]
[Applause]
wrapped around her flimsy little fin she
will be our inn she'll be what we use
baby can reviews
[Music]
trust me fellas
[Applause]
my
[Music]
ariel
he doesn't understand me
he doesn't even try
i've never felt at home here
homes with your family
isn't it
what if home isn't the place you were
born
what if it's a place you have to
discover for yourself
i'd miss you if you were gone you would
well
not in a dopey way
not in a crazy hopeless i'm so in love
but she doesn't even know i exist kind
of way
not like that at all
ah
gotta go
flounder you're very sweet
daddy's never even met a human yet
he only thinks the worst of them
i just don't see how a world that makes
such wonderful things
could be so
bad look at this stuff
isn't it neat
wouldn't you think my collection's
complete
wouldn't you think i'm the girl
the girl who has
everything
look at this trove
treasures untold
how many wonders can one cavern hold
looking around here you think
sure she's got everything
i've got gadgets and gizmos plenty
i've got who's it
you want thingamabobs
i got 20.
but who cares
[Music]
flipping your fins you don't get too far
legs are required for jumping dancing
strolling on down the road what's that
word again
streets
up where they walk
up where they run
up where they stay all day in the sun
wandering free
wish i could be
part of that world
what would i give
if i could live out of these waters
what would i pay
to spend a day
[Applause]
[Music]
bright young women
is
[Music]
wish i could be
part of that
[Music]
[Applause]
child
you got trouble in the mind sebastian
what is all this just just a few
knickknacks i've collected that that's
all
you ought to be ashamed of yourself if
your poor father knew about this place
bastion you're not gonna tell him are
you please he'd never understand
listen to me ariel for my sake as well
as your own it's time you kept your mind
on your music
from now on you'll have voice lessons
every single day
and perhaps you can pick up an
instrument
something ladylike
da harp maybe
why sure a nice hob
made out of stripped wood decorated with
mother of pearl
arielle
somebody's got to nail this girl's fins
to the floor arielle
[Music]
me
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
i don't want to be king
i swore no to your father on his
deathbed oh may god bless his soul that
i would turn you from the rent rousabout
into a proper royal so you are worthy to
fill his shoes eric now you're making me
greasy grimsby and that's not all
i also promised i'd have you married by
your next birthday married our kingdom
needs a queen sire have you ever tried
to take a princess sailing grimsby it's
a joke
they're crindling get caught in the
rigging
and besides most of them can't even swim
swim sire is that a prerequisite
sure if we go sailing
where am i going to find her grimsby
a girl who's as carefree and alive is to
see itself
where
well what do you know that'll be quiet
they'll hear you oh i got you i got you
for being in trepidation
[Music]
it's too much to hope for
isn't it
but somewhere out there
it's a girl
who's a match for a guy like me
perhaps you're not looking hot enough
i've never been this close to a human
before
me neither i thought you were an expert
on their stuffed shore but e gads the
sight of them
horrible that square jaw those broad
shoulders and two eyes of the same color
there's no variety
i don't know
i think he's really handsome
you do
oh
trust me grimsby
when i find the girl in my dreams
it'll hit me
like lightning
hurricane
[Music]
don't worry grimsby i'll get you home
safely
[Music]
[Applause]
was i too late
it's hard to say
i can't make out a heartbeat
no look
he's breathing
oh scott look at him
he's so beautiful
what would i give to live for where you
are
what would i pay
to stay here
beside you what would i do to see you
smiling at me
where would we walk
where would we run
if we could stay all day in the sun
[Music]
quick kid you better get going before we
divulge
somebody anybody
oh get away
[Music]
oh eric
you just adore making my pulse race
don't you
[Music]
a girl rescued me
she pulled me right out of the surf
and she was
singing
there there he had a terrible tumble my
boy
her voice
i can't get it out of my head
it's the sound of the sea that's all
no
i'll prove it to you
i'll find her
and i'll thank her for saving my life
you best come with me a good night's
sleep and you'll be good as new
no please
you have to believe me you've heard to
me tall tales my boy no
she was real grimsby
yes of course she was
as real as a siren as real as mermaids
on rocks
i don't know when
i don't know how
but i know something started right now
watch
[Music]
ariel is working my last nerf acting
like a big fish in a small pond so i'm
an option when everybody else is
swimming down if you ask me because
she's a pie
no question about it she sure is acting
fishy lately she's dizzy and she's
dreamy her head's up in the foam her
eyes have gone all gleamie it's like
there's no one home she floats away the
days who open on the coastal shelf
watch her where she's going she giggles
like a fool she barely sticks a toe and
down at the tidal pool it's more
[Music]
oh
i think she's even wearing brand new
[Music]
she doesn't even speak she treats me
like sashimi left over from last week
you see her late at night tossing in her
ocean
[Music]
[Applause]
and she's
[Music]
she
swimming in the sea k
is good
[Music]
she's
[Applause]
[Music]
look
she
[Music]
audience or ariel
that sister of yours is as slippery as
an eel where has she swam off to now i
gotta find her for her daddy goes
looking
good luck she's in la la land
that girl's head over tails love
in love
audience come on flounder who's the
lucky merman
oh gee i don't know didn't even know it
was love until the second chorus oh come
on flounder you know her better than
anyone you follow her everywhere
not anymore
not since she started chasing after
humans
i hope and pray i didn't just say humans
and this new love of hers don't tell me
and don't ask me he's won a damn a real
human the four-legged kind daddy's gonna
be where oh dating outside of her
species thanks flounder you're a real
angel fish
water all around your child and you
still got to play with fire
[Music]
where did she go
where can she be
[Music]
when will she come again
calling to me
calling to
me
[Applause]
somewhere there's a girl there's like
the shimmer of the wind upon the water
the glimmer of the sunlight on the sea
somewhere there's a girl
[Music]
somewhere she is singing and her song is
meant for me
[Music]
is sweet as angels
and her
voice is warm as summer skies
[Music]
[Applause]
her voice
with all due respect sire you've been
scouring the sea for weeks and to what
end
i vowed to find her and i will
i have a better idea
on the eve of your 21st birthday will
host a marvelous ball
we'll invite countless eligible young
lady i knew it to sing for you
[Music]
what a contest what better way to find
your mysterious voice than that
you'll be married by sunset on that very
same day just as your father decreed
yes
why yes that's how we'll find her indeed
we shall you have my word
she's out there somewhere
i just know it
i can censor laughter in the ripple of
the waves against the shoreline
[Music]
i can see her smiling in the moonlight
as it settles on the side
[Music]
singing out a melody too lovely to
withstand
[Music]
and her
voice is there as dawn
steals by
pure and bright
it's always near all day all night and
still i hear it called
her
strange as a dream
[Music]
realize the sea
if you can hear me now
come set me free
come set me
free
[Music]
[Applause]
uh
child there you are
a human
you fell in love with a human
i didn't choose it it just
happened oh child i thought maybe just
maybe you'd be happy for me
happy for you
happy
cause you're gone plum crazy now
child it's time you get your head out of
the clouds and back in the water where
it belongs but i don't belong here i've
never fit in as hard as i try
if only i could be up there instead
walking on the very same ground he is
breathing the very same air
down here is your home
the human world
it's a mess
life under the sea is better than
anything negotiated you're wrong i swear
believe me child it's true
the seaweed is always greener in
somebody else's lake
you dream about going up there but that
is a big mistake
just look at the world around you right
here on your channel
things around ya what more is you
looking for
under the sea
darling it's better down where it's
where to take it from me
up on the shore they work all day out in
the sun they slave away when the wedding
[Music]
is
we got no troubles
[Music]
[Applause]
and all that
[Music]
[Applause]
wow
[Music]
[Applause]
uh
[Music]
[Applause]
music to me
[Music]
under
[Applause]
see child and that's what i'm talking
about
ariel
[Music]
hello sebastian where is she
you just miss her she slip away i think
she'd betray her family in this way turn
her back on her own kind she can't help
it saya i taught her myself now she's
making a mockery of everything we hold
dear
where is she hiding
if i only knew she keeps secrets from me
sebastian not from you a wager you know
where she is
now take me to her
[Music]
to think that this belonged to him once
he held it in his own two hands
tell the truth did you save a human from
drowning
who told
which one of you
i'm sorry ariel
i'm nothing but a guppy just a lousy
lousy guppy
you get every single solo and it isn't
fair that's enough leave us alone
you too sebastian
so did you
i had to rescue the prince you had to
without me he would have perished he's a
human you are a mermaid i can't hate him
just because he's different
perhaps you can
but it's just not in me
different
they catch us with their nets they spare
us with their blade
they're not all like that have you
forgotten what they did to your mother
we can't know that for certain can there
be any doubt she slips out one more in
pronounce and swim and never returns
you can't
i know in my heart and that's enough
murderers all of them
you can't blame all humans for a few
wicked ones i will not have you build a
shrine to them
worshiping the rut
they're the breeders selling them
[Music]
again
audience
[Music]
ruined all of my things
my human stuff
if he really and truly love me or child
it's because he loves you
it sure is a funny way of showing it
he can break every single treasure i own
but he can't break me
well you just might break his heart and
you
some friend you turned out to be
bringing me here to my secret place
for your own good child i pray you wake
up from this madness
and soon you're swimming in some
dangerous waters
if only he would look
if only he could see
he could love me as i am instead of how
he wished i'd be
he doesn't really care
he doesn't want to know
i hate him yes i hate him oh i hate him
so
and oh what i would give if only i
caused
poor child sweet child she has a
very serious problem hasn't she
[Music]
and worry
you can't possibly mean
aunt ursula
she knows your true father says her
magic is evil
please i have to go
she'll cast a child
[Music]
together
forever
[Music]
where did you go
ariel darling it's me
you're auntie ursula i shouldn't be here
nonsense darling we're family
father says you're wicked and hateful oh
yes but he says the same things about
humans too doesn't he snookums and we
both know that's not true don't we
why did he banish you there wasn't
enough ocean for the both of us and now
he's driven you away too
he doesn't understand me oh but i do
dumpling we are very much like you and i
gals with ambition nothing scares a man
more does it
now
tell dear old auntie
everything
i'm i'm in love with someone oh
a human oh yes
this prince fellow well he's quite the
catch
the answer is simple
you've got to become human yourself
can you help me
oh
my dear
child it's what i live for
to help
unfortunate merfolk like yourself
poor souls with no one else to turn to
i admit that in the past i've been a
nasty they weren't kidding when they
called me well a witch
but you'll find that nowadays i've
mended all my ways and repented seeing
the light made a switch true yes and i
fortunately know a little magic it's a
talent that i always have possessed
and here lately praise her math i use it
on behalf of the miserable lonely and
depressed pathetic poor unfortunate
songs in pain
in need this one longing to be not that
one wants to get the girl and do i help
them
yes indeed
those poor fortunate souls so sad
so true
they can flock into my college and
grinds fails i slap these and i help
them
yes i do
now it's happened once or twice someone
couldn't pay the price and i'm afraid i
had to rake them across the calls
yes i've had the odd complaint but on
the whole i've been a state to those
poor unfortunate souls
here's my best offer baby kins
i know a spell that will turn you into a
human for three days
now it's got a procedural clause sort of
a squid pro quo
before the sun sets on the third day
you've got to get dear or princey to
kiss you
if you do you'll stay human forever
and if i don't oh nothing drastic
darling i'm sure oh look small print
your soul is mine forever and you're
doomed to spend eternity in my watcher
hell so glare lawyers
don't you just love them
of course there is one more thing
my fee
but i don't have anything i'm not asking
for much
only
your voice
my voice
don't worry darling i have the perfect
place for it
your grandpappy poseidon gave us trident
to your father but this was his gift for
moi your magic shell you've heard about
it
father's is the source of all your
witchcraft not said stalling he says you
you die without it die
oh please it's merely a bubble a vessel
for your voice
trust me darling your vibrato your
legato even your belt you'll all be safe
and sound in here
but if i give away my voice how can i f
you'll have your looks
your pretty face
and don't underestimate the power
men up there don't like a lot of blabber
ah they think a girl who gossips is a
bore
yes on land it's much preferred for
ladies not to say a word and after all
do you wear this idol prattle for come
on out of that impressed with
conversation
true gentlemen avoid it when they can
but they don't tune in on a lady who's
withdrawn is she who holds her tongue
who gets her man come on you
unfortunately
[Music]
just your voice
so sad
so true
if you want to cross that bridge my
sweets you gotta pay the toll take a
gulp and take a breath go ahead and sign
the school some jets and now i got
a voice the bus
[Music]
so
so how about it cupcake but if i become
human i'll never see my family again
my sisters even my father now do you
want princy poor not
five
four
three
two yes
yes i'll do it
where do i sign
not just any ink darling
use mine
[Music]
[Applause]
the fortune to me
now sing
sing your voice over to me
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
wow
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
so
foreign
well look who got beached
wait there's something different about
you nope nope don't tell me i'll
deciphen it for myself
now
hmm
it's your hairdo you've been using the
dinglehopper she's got legs you idiot
she traded her voice to the sea witch
and got legs
no not your beautiful pipes
you see not a sound
ah kid it hurts me to say but that
that was a lousy swap
what would her father say i'll tell you
what her father would say her father
would say he'd kill himself a crab
that's what he'd say he's got just three
days three days to what make the prince
fall in love with her
and to prove it he gets to
i mean he's
got to
kiss her
oh the prince well if you want to snare
the prince you got to learn a graceful
way of perambulating she'll do no such
thing sure she will come on now upsy
daisy
what's this you giving up so soon that's
not like you gotta have a little
gumption a candy kind of attitude take
it from a gull who knows you look at me
you see this face in terms of beauty i'm
a basket case and as for style and sour
farewell i guess there ain't a whole lot
there yeah although perhaps it makes no
sense i struck my stuff with lots of
confidence cause though i lack an awful
lot there is one thing i got i got
positivity
i got positivity
it
[Music]
there ain't nothing you can't do
and that's how positivity works for you
positivity why there's no such word sure
there is it's in the dictionary right
between popsuckle and prehysterical and
believe you me i've seen the word
miracles
you see it's really your prerogative you
simply can't think cognitive then
there's you just sitting there smack
down flat upon your derriere if that's
the way you wanna be well you might as
well be shrubbery so stand right up in
just a seat and walk real tall upon your
own feet and show you'll trip and make
mistakes but you've got what it takes
[Music]
ah
uh
[Music]
and just let that pause the tree no
positivity
what is it
[Applause]
[Music]
yeah what is going on here
shoo
huh get away shoo
miss
are you all right
[Music]
you seem very familiar
do i know you from somewhere
of course
i've been looking for you everywhere
please you must tell me what's your name
excuse me you don't speak english
oh it's for our throat eh
oh
i'm sorry
you don't speak at all do you
for a moment i confuse you with someone
else
[Music]
what is it
do you need help
a bit dizzy aren't you
i've got just the remedy
come on now
the palace isn't far
bravo ariel now that's what i call
reeling them in
this is gonna get me in a real hot water
you believe this guy what a crab
and now you know that word
there ain't nothing you can't do
and that's how positivity
works for you
[Music]
so
your majesty
have you found her we searched
everywhere we found no trace of your
daughter
well keep looking until you do yes sire
i never meant to wish her ill daddy i
know
but
if she never returns and i'm forced to
sing her solos don't call us
i'm sorry daddy
we won't rest
not until she's home
thank you dear child as if the loss of
your mother wasn't enough
[Music]
perhaps a horrible shipwreck will never
know the truth she won't speak not a
single solitary word
do what you must to make her presentable
a screw up in the tub a proper frog
[Music]
getting strength back dearie
i can't help but wonder what she must be
thinking
i'd give a birthing or two
just to hear her thoughts
[Music]
oh
but not
like
this
look over there oh my gosh how very odd
and what might they be something
splendid maybe look over here could you
bust isn't it just me dazzling daisy
utterly amazing gazing around it's like
to die
just seen it feel so good i'd scream if
i only could i'd hoped and wished and
wanted so to be here wished and prayed
and planted to a team
prayed and wow just look it's really me
here walking around streams that seems
somewhere beyond my wild history
look at her there looking round won't
make a sound keeps on
[Music]
just picture
ladies in two short days the prince will
be holding a contest and the young
ladies everywhere will be seeing
themselves silly all to win his heart
tonight he'll savor some quiet
[Music]
i talked and wished and wondered what
i'd do here wished and prayed and
pictured what i'd see
pray and wow my prayers are coming true
here look at it all look how it gleams
lovely beyond my wildest dreams
it's him
[Music]
so handsome and refined and slim
sweet
[Music]
from head to toe
and all
i
told and wished
my life would feel enchanted
my prayers are more than granted
look at it all whole left your hall
perfect as you could please hear more
and even more jury dimension is here and
who knows
[Music]
just look at me and you will see someone
beyonce
[Music]
[Applause]
good evening
well
no i'm the one who's speechless
hungry
[Music]
escargot
lobster beast
tuna tatar
holy mackerel maintenant
[Music]
[Applause]
me
[Music]
first i cut
a cleaver i hack them in
i pull out what's inside and i serve it
up fry oh i love little fishes don't you
here's something for tempting the
palette
preparation's a classic technique
first two pounds of fish fluff was a
mallet
then you slash through the skin gives a
belly a slice then you rub some salted
cause that makes it taste nice
[Music]
i have missed one
sacred blue
what is this
how on earth could i release
such a sweet little succulent crab
gel domage what a loss you belong in the
sauce with some flour i think
[Music]
cause it's gonna be hot
in my big copper pot
dude
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
it's been a long time hasn't it prince
eric since we dined in the presence of
such loveliness
usually it's just me and grim
he has to look across the table at my
ugly mug
the bath has certainly done its wonders
she's groomed for a groom as you might
say easy old boy easy
isn't that unusual
yes indeed
thank you
[Music]
oh don't tell me she's fond of tobacco
too
oh the pipe i can't say i blame you it's
an old antique mayor shawn from
dusseldorf
[Music]
looks like your pipe smoked you all boy
yes
very amusing
she certainly knows how to make you
laugh doesn't she
now you two enjoy each other i'm off to
the beach
[Music]
and now something truly exquisite
a delectable treat what i'm sure he'll
just love
[Music]
if it's killed it's been grilled to a
tea
fish lightly toasted and roasted and
[Music]
steamy and now for the grand finale la
pierce de resistance a delicacy by golly
you won't find in restaurants
i did to tease your taste buds with that
certain shouldn't say
voila
[Music]
that's him
[Applause]
[Music]
catch him
[Applause]
[Music]
just look at the two of us a couple of
misfits
you're a quiet girl in a noisy world and
i'm a prince who'd rather be a sailor
we're both
fish out of water you and i
what is it
did i say something wrong
i'm sorry
who needs words anyway
a smile can say just as much sometimes
nimble on your feet aren't you
dancing beats small talk any day
sure it's the way your feet smile
or laugh
it lets you say so many things
dancing is a language that is felt
instead of hurt
you can whisper sing or shout without so
much as a word
try it
go on
like so
just let your emotions tell your body
what to do
see how much a single gesture can reveal
and every little step
every single step
is one step closer
to saying what you feel
once the music hits you inhibitions fall
away and you find that you're expressing
things your voice there and say
don't be afraid let's go
as soon as you surrender what's inside
we'll sweep on through as the boundaries
between us disappear
and every little stop
every single step is one step closer
to talking loud and clear
oh that's just like a conversation
except you never need to make a sound
and once you've begun
you speak as one give and take
back and forth round and round
[Applause]
so
foreign
[Applause]
oh dad
is like a conversation
except your lips don't ever need
and to you've begun
you speak as one cheek to achieve
toe-to-toe
heart to heart
dancing is a language that is felt
instead of hurt
but it says much more than
and language little step
every single step
is one step closer
one step closer
[Applause]
one step closer to
being understood
do you hear that
[Music]
i'm sorry
i haven't been myself lately
it's past midnight
i should let you get some sleep
good night
out of the frying pan
into the fire the things i do for you
young lady
now i know what i should do i should
march you right back home to your father
so you can be miserable the rest of your
life
it's true
i got no backbone
all right child
i'm in
now we got to make a plan for that boy
to kiss ya before it's too late
first you gotta bat your eyes lighties
you gotta pucker your lips like this
oh that's good you put those two things
together and you got the boy in the palm
of your hand
all right child off to bed with you
[Music]
that was too close for comfort boys
one day and they're already dining
together and the dancing
i should have known
there's only one thing more potent than
my black magic the power of srila
teenage hormones
seems a little tart
is often quite a start
just one night of principle is wallowing
in bless
think of what they'll do by sensing
number two
[Music]
yes you're
wretchedness baby
[Music]
daddy and his angels how they're gonna
hurt
yes
[Applause]
hahaha
[Music]
[Applause]
no girls ever dared to join me out here
before
too afraid they'd muddy their shoes
but not
you
peaceful
isn't it
not another living soul for miles and
miles
nothing is happening they spent all
morning on horseback a dinner picnic and
now peace and not so much as a pick on
the cheek
so
how about this weather
this is going nowhere fast 24 hours left
he'll be married off in ariel she'll be
deep
we've got to do something and quick
but what
we got to create the right kind of mood
ooh
something romantical like candlelight
and shampoo
nonsense it don't take all that
everything we need we got right here
percussion
[Music]
[Applause]
and words
[Music]
and you don't
yes
[Music]
not
sing with me now
[Music]
[Applause]
you know i really ought to know your
name
[Music]
maybe i could guess
alexandra
annabelle
beatrice
[Applause]
ariel
hey
that's kind of pretty
all right
ariel
now
[Music]
[Applause]
don't be scared you want to
go on
[Music]
[Applause]
yes
[Music]
[Applause]
sebastian
what was that
lightning
from underwater
ariel
are you all right
must have been some kind of freak storm
we ought to head back
tomorrow's my birthday
and we're hosting a contest
grimsby wants me to be married by sunset
or else
[Music]
[Applause]
one
so
most merciful triton i pray you keep
calm where is she sebastian where is
eria she'd be so angry if she knew i was
here i entrusted my youngest daughter
and what happens i have have you cracked
i have to have you shell he almost wants
your greatness and all for ariel and you
you have to be ashamed of yourself too
what kind of tragedy will it take
a tragedy involving the sea witch to be
exact what did you say
well
these two eels came and they took her
show right to ursula and she treated her
voice for a pair of legs and if the
prince doesn't kiss her voice she's not
around a voice to become a human
by sunset tomorrow that girl could be
giving up her very soul
her soul
and all to that wicked sister of yours
it's time i end things with her
once and for all
[Music]
pardon me young lady anything else you
require
oh very well then you best catch 40
wings it's a big day tomorrow prince
eric must choose a bride
looks so blue
the secret to happiness to your child
we mustn't wish
for impossible things
if only you could know
the things i longed to say
if only i could tell you what i wish i
could convey
[Music]
if only you would look
only you could glimpse the feeling that
i feel
if only you would notice what i'm dying
to reveal
the dreams i can't declare
if it means
you would
[Music]
would be broken
what is it about her that's so
wonderfully impossibly familiar
why do i feel dizzy in a way i've only
found it once before
how come when she looks at me it seems
like time stops
almost like the way you did that day
upon the show
[Music]
[Applause]
so
[Music]
tomorrow the prince will have his pick
of any princess in the land
how can a little mermaid compete with
that
if only i knew how
[Music]
[Applause]
dreams come true
and wouldn't that surprise you if you're
only how could i have pushed her to the
point of having nowhere left to turn
to
what if i have lost her and it's all my
fault she's gone
[Music]
[Applause]
i'll keep my temper low
i should have started listening
[Music]
but i'll lose
me
[Music]
[Applause]
ah
[Music]
[Applause]
welcome dear friends to our contest
the first that this kingdom has ever
seen
we gather today for a vocal display so
our prince may at last choose a queen
these six princesses possess the most
accomplished voices in all the land
tonight one of you yes one of you will
go home with the crown may the best
woman win
i'm so excited
[Music]
that's not the voice i'll know it the
moment i hear it
[Music]
you think i'm the girl the girl who has
everything
[Music]
can't you hear
surely one of these lovely voices
matches the music in your heart eric
i wish i could say yes
but she's not here
well her father's the rule of all
pressure
no go back
she's got good birthing hips
no okay
she's one of triplets but they're
willing to break up the set no grimsby
oh what am i to do the sun is nearly set
your birthday is almost over you must
choose somebody perhaps if we steal
ourselves take another listen please
[Applause]
you mustn't wait grimsby
be quiet
and listen
go ahead ariel
[Music]
oh poor child poor lost child
i had so hoped eric that you would find
love somewhere in this room
perhaps i have
i've just been too blind to see it
but that's impossible she did another
sound no
well i heard every single note
as clear as a bell
now that must mean something old boy
perhaps it does
could it be another contestant that's it
that's the voice oh my goodness
[Music]
tell her she's two ways
tell her the competition
oh why look what a glorious sunset and
on the third day too
time's up lover boy
you
[Music]
down losers
to the depths where you
[Music]
belong goodbye to your prince your
pretty dress you're satin punks you're
my now mermaid
prepare to spend the rest of your days
as her slave
and plucking
the barnacles
[Music]
ursa
brother darling you're right on cue what
have you done with my daughter why
nothing she's done it all to herself
trading her voice away and for what
human heartbreak give her back to me
not on your life it so happens that your
daughter signed a contract what
even drew little heart above the eye
is it finding goodness yes
unbreakable unless unless there is a
little something we could try go on
perhaps we could arrange a sort of
trade-off
maybe swap your dodger soul for say your
own sign the scroll and set her free
or else she comes with me
to suffer for eternity
the mute little hatchling drowning in
her own sorrow with no voice left to cry
out your name
well i'm waiting
it's not my soul you're after it's my
power which would you rather be
the king of the sea
or a father to his little girl
finally the oceans belong to me
[Music]
and now you poor unfortunate soul
now the power of poseidon has been once
again made whole all the magic of the
trident down the shell in my control and
now dog shall reign forever
[Music]
now see for yourself how banishment
feels
[Music]
my black magic now
my
the smell voice
broken give me back my shell if it
breaks
you die
you believe that after all the lies he's
told you
lies what what
you told her that the world above was
hideous and what was it instead
beautiful
beautiful beyond compare he'd say
anything to turn you against the prince
in his kind why he's shameless he'd even
they murdered your mother wait
if humans didn't kill my mother
then who did
it was you wasn't
all these years i've been blaming humans
when it was you
who what why i could learn a minute
[Music]
daddy
can you ever forgive me
i caused you such terrible worry
thinking only of myself
not you not my sisters not this place
the only place i've ever truly called my
home no no ariel i'm the one who's at
fault blaming humans there's goodness in
people daddy i know i've seen it even
when i couldn't
i'm proud of you erin and your mother
would be too
somehow in the blink of an eye when my
back was dead
you grew up
you love him very much don't you
it's what she wants your majesty
please
[Applause]
[Music]
you belong to his world now
thank you teddy thank you so much
[Music]
[Applause]
tomorrow at sunrise we will search again
oh but majesty she's lost i won't rest
until i found her grimsby
[Music]
ariel eric
could it be
it's been your voice all along hasn't it
who are you this is my father i'm king
triton astonishing i must say defies all
possibility
your majesty
at last i found someone who makes me
eager to seize the future
and claim my birthright is king
but if i slip out to sea sometimes
she won't mind
she'll be right there next to me keeping
us both on course
with your permission
i'd like to make her my wife
my permission
ariel can speak for herself
ariel
yes eric oh yes
this can't be happening
no more grog after bedtime bad idea
and you're the young man's father
heavens no his majesty's long gone i'm
his guardian nothing more well i wager
he'd be very proud of the both of you
why thank you sire he's my one shining
achievement a bright light in a very
dark world well congratulations to us
both my friend
and to you yes
and to you
must be a human thing
[Music]
so
my
before me you could stay
and never say goodbye
if only i could make time stop believe
me i would try
but fathers have to learn that daughters
have to grow
and if you truly love them you must let
them go
[Music]
tall tales and superstitions hey grimsby
so that's truly the king of the sea and
she's his daughter does that upset you
no no no i'm just glad she's royalty
[Music]
[Applause]
sailing forward
[Music]
is
[Applause]
[Music]
just you and me
and i will be
[Music]
[Applause]
so
[Music]
[Applause]
okay
[Music]
[Applause]
so
[Music]
[Applause]
life under the sea is better than
anything they got
the seaweed is always greener in
somebody else's lake
you dream about going up there but that
is a big mistake
just look at the world around ya right
here on your channel
such wonderful things around ya what
more is you looking for
under the sea
[Music]
[Applause]
since life is
[Music]
[Applause]
on the street